<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Welcome to Lab Five</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/</id><updated>2021-02-08T19:25:00-07:00</updated><entry><title>Bye bye</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/bye-bye.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T19:25:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T19:25:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/bye-bye.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I gotta go, Mom said it's my bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Reject social media, return to monke</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/reject-social-media-return-to-monke.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T19:15:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T19:15:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/reject-social-media-return-to-monke.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If the last 10 years have proved anything, it's that Mark Zuckerberg is a reptile and doesn't have human emotions. Through his devil's work that is Facebook he endeavours to rid the world of all positive emotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Save us, Lab Five!" I hear you plea. Well, don't worry, because I …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If the last 10 years have proved anything, it's that Mark Zuckerberg is a reptile and doesn't have human emotions. Through his devil's work that is Facebook he endeavours to rid the world of all positive emotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Save us, Lab Five!" I hear you plea. Well, don't worry, because I have a solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Apply to work at Facebook. Grind leetcode (more on that one later). Get the interview. Pass it. Get the on-site interview. And when you go to the on-site interview, pack an EMP in your backpack. THEN, when your interviewer asks you to reverse fizzbuzz or whatever, you whip out your emp and say "reverse THIS!!!!" then you hit the button onn the EMP and delete Facebook!!! That's what happens when you BREAK UP WITH ME REBECCA YOU GET YOUR FACEBOOK DELETED!!!!!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;w&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>JAMstack is overrated</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/jamstack-is-overrated.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T19:10:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T19:10:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/jamstack-is-overrated.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here's another trend that won't last the end of the year: JAMstack. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is jamsnack? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically a bunch of frontend developers wanted to do backend stuff but didn't want to have to, &lt;em&gt;like, do any work or stuff.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen, I think static sites are cool too, but can we just …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here's another trend that won't last the end of the year: JAMstack. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is jamsnack? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically a bunch of frontend developers wanted to do backend stuff but didn't want to have to, &lt;em&gt;like, do any work or stuff.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listen, I think static sites are cool too, but can we just keep it simple and in the database? That's what they are for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This whole thing just seems like an exit scheme for Netlify.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe I'll make my own new web framework paradigm. PeanutButterStack. Yeah, and it'll be way better than jam stack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm hungry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>LinkedIn is a stain upon the web</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/linkedin-is-a-stain-upon-the-web.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T19:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T19:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/linkedin-is-a-stain-upon-the-web.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ah yes, Facebook but for managers. Just the thought of using it gives me a disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever used LinkedIn?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God it is awful. Badly designed and badly coded. It's effectively just another way for advertisers to make us insecure. The worst part? Some professionals actually take it seriously …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ah yes, Facebook but for managers. Just the thought of using it gives me a disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever used LinkedIn?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;God it is awful. Badly designed and badly coded. It's effectively just another way for advertisers to make us insecure. The worst part? Some professionals actually take it seriously. I'll begrudgingly copy my resume to it, but there's no way on this side of the underworld that I will interact with people on LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I gladly await the day that I can become a senior-something professional and finally release my soul from the dungeons of LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever I have to log into LinkedIn I play my favourite song on repeat until the ordeal is over:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="500" height="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TnDC0JAcYp0" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Hello Blog</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/hello-blog.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T17:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T17:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/hello-blog.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Finally I have a way to distribute my complaints unto the world without getting cancelled on twitter. Let us begin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Leetcode is for suckers</title><link href="https://hughbagan.github.io/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/leetcode-is-for-suckers.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-02-08T11:47:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T11:47:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Hug</name></author><id>tag:hughbagan.github.io,2021-02-08:/CMPUT404Wi21-lab5/leetcode-is-for-suckers.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;(Ok so im writing this post on my Mom's ipad i stole it because she doesn't let me go on my computer past my bedtime.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leetcode is for suckers. What, you wanna work at Google or facebook or whatever? One problem with that: you actually have to go and live …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;(Ok so im writing this post on my Mom's ipad i stole it because she doesn't let me go on my computer past my bedtime.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leetcode is for suckers. What, you wanna work at Google or facebook or whatever? One problem with that: you actually have to go and live at the google place when you're an employee. You know how much of a dump san francisco is these days? Yeah, have fun with that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most important puzzle piece: there's now a market catering to these kinds of people. Books, videos, articles-- whatever-- are being sold to you if you're a part of this crowd. Even if this is what you want to do, please PLEASE don't be a sucker and buy in to what the idiots on youtube say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a thought: instead of working at some esoteric company in a literal different country, try applying to the good companies in your area. I guarantee they need software developers too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And stop stressing about it, that stuff takes years off your life you know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you're an employer or recruiter reading this, just admit to yourself that you don't even know Kruskall's algorithm either. Your company isn't special.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway yeah any job that you have to interview for &amp;gt;6 months for is a scam.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Blog"></category></entry></feed>